[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Brian Hegland won a 1997 Razzie and a 1997 Oscar for different movies. In which category did he win?", "correct_answer": "Best/Worst  Screenplay", "incorrect_answers": ["Best /Worst Actor", "Best/ Worst Song", "Best/Worst Director"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1984, they became the first rap group to have an album certified gold.", "correct_answer": "Run-D.M.C.", "incorrect_answers": ["Sugarhill Gang", "Naughty By Nature", "Soul II Soul"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the command module of Apollo 11?", "correct_answer": "Columbia", "incorrect_answers": ["Eagle", "Georgia", "Thunder"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the last name of the characters played by Meryl Streep and Dustin Hoffman in a 1979 drama?", "correct_answer": "Kramer", "incorrect_answers": ["Rowe", "Wade", "Brown"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which US state is nicknamed The Pine Tree State?", "correct_answer": "Maine", "incorrect_answers": ["New Hampshire", "Missouri", "Massachusetts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is a basic ingredients of the summer yogurt soup called tarator, very popular on the Balkans?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Cucumber", "Dill", "Garlic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first performer to have both the Billboard number one and number two album?", "correct_answer": "Bob Newhart", "incorrect_answers": ["Willie Nelson", "Frank Sinatra", "Johnny Mathis"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "India Pale Ale was originally made in India.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Are all dolphins considered whales?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1991 movie has this tag?  Each of us is matched somewhere in the world, by our exact double - someone who shares our thoughts and dreams", "correct_answer": "The Double Life of V\u00e9ronique", "incorrect_answers": ["Delicatessen", "The City of Lost Children", "Three Lives and Only One Death"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The term nosophobia denotes the fear of telling lies.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is the symbol for Plutonium on the Periodic Table of Elements?", "correct_answer": "Pu", "incorrect_answers": ["P", "Pt", "Pm"]}]